{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Chapter7_2.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [
                "i'll take"
            ],
            "answer": "I take",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518547471.7369099,
            "question": "Given the definition \"prendo\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "Allora Giulia, che cosa prendi?",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1518547503.9967668,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Well, Giulia, what are you having?\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I'll have the bruschette of the house",
                "I would like the bruschette of the house"
            ],
            "answer": "I would like the bruschette of the house.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518547497.0766606,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Vorrei le bruschette della casa.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ordino anche il vino",
                "Ordino anche, il vino?",
                "ordino anche il vino?"
            ],
            "answer": "Ordino anche il vino?",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1518547513.2767627,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Shall I order wine, too?\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il maiale al forno",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518547464.9175096,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the pork roast\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "squisito"
            ],
            "answer": "squisito/squisita/squisiti/squisite",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518547487.224447,
            "question": "Given the definition \"delicious\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Possiamo pagare con la carta di credito",
                "possiamo pagare con la carta di credito"
            ],
            "answer": "Possiamo pagare con la carta di credito?",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518547484.145092,
            "question": "Can we pay by credit card?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Well Giulia, what will you have?",
                "Well Giulia, what are you having?"
            ],
            "answer": "Well, Giulia, what are you having?",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518547459.0771482,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Allora Giulia, che cosa prendi?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "ordinate",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1455122129.5660589,
            "question": "Voi (ordinare) il primo.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I'll have the appetizer"
            ],
            "answer": "I order the antipasto.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518547523.8003106,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Io ordino l'antipasto.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "bene, chiamo subito il cameriere"
            ],
            "answer": "Bene, chaimo subito il cameriere.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147853.0626612,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"All right, I'll call the waiter right away.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "prendi",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"you take\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "Si, certo: mezzo litro di (vino) rosso della casa. E una bottiglia di acqua minerale naturale.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518548651.5033035,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Yes, sure. Half a liter of the house red. And a bottle of mineral water, still.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "E cosa prendi per primo?",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1454955682.820712,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"And what are you having as a first course?\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "you ask for",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1486406277.7809372,
            "question": "Given the definition \"chiedi\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "prendo i ravioli; sono molto buoni",
                "Prendo i ravioli; sono molto buoni"
            ],
            "answer": "Prendo i ravioli; sono molto buoni.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1486147433.560607,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I'll have the ravioli; they're very good.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "chiama",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1454955686.61278,
            "question": "chiamare (lui/lei)",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Buono idea! Io invece vorrei il maiale al forno con contorno di patate.",
                "Buona idea! Io invece vorrei il maiale al forno con contorno di potate."
            ],
            "answer": "Buona idea. Io invece vorrei il maiale al forno con contorno di patate.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1486407228.1525202,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Good idea! I'd like the pork roast with a side of potatoes instead.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "chiede",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1454955676.2230499,
            "question": "chidere (lui/lei)",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "C'e' un ufficio postale qui vicino?",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1486407128.7433362,
            "question": "Is there a post office nearby?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "Il divano di Carla e' vecchio.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1454955130.6907837,
            "question": "Carla's couch is old.",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Ordino il pesce alla griglia",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1454696912.25154,
            "question": "I order the grilled fish.",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Si, la carne e' eccellente. Prendo una bistecca con contorno di insalata"
            ],
            "answer": "Si, la carne e' eccellente. Prendo una bistecca con contorno di insalata.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1486406274.101317,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Yes, the meat is excellent. I'll have a beefsteak with a side of salad.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "vorrei l'acqua minerale"
            ],
            "answer": "Vorrei l'acqua minerale",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1486061259.3340983,
            "question": "I would like the mineral water.",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "chiedo",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1454696900.1115398,
            "question": "chidere (io)",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Lui prende il dolce.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1454955353.2753098,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"He takes the dessert.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "prende",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1454955655.6273358,
            "question": "prendere (lui/lei)",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "tu prendi i ravioli al ragu'",
                "tu prendi i ravioli al ragu",
                "tu prendi i ravioli al ragu?"
            ],
            "answer": "Tu prendi i ravioli al ragu'.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1486147803.3956907,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You (informal) take the ravioli with meat sauce.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Are you having a main course, too?",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1454955036.0098822,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Prendi anche il secondo?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "pmodoro e basilico",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1455122116.784781,
            "question": "Given the definition \"tomato and basil\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "you pay",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1454955113.838378,
            "question": "Given the definition \"paghi\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "posso avere la carta di vini?"
            ],
            "answer": "Posso avere la carta di vini?",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1486061738.192459,
            "question": "May I have the wine list?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "prendi anche il secondo",
                "prendi anche il secondo?"
            ],
            "answer": "Prendi anche il secondo?",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1486147755.417212,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Are you having a main course, too?\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ordinano",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1486406984.6379588,
            "question": "Loro (ordinare) la bistecca.",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "paga",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1454955792.7666085,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"he/she pays\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "prende",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1455122107.444847,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"he/she takes\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Nella camera c'e' il letto matrimoniale.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1455122076.0837111,
            "question": "In the bedroom there is the double bed.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the pork roast",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486061244.0264332,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il maiale al forno\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Lei ordina la frutta.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1454955313.9455366,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"She orders the fruit.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "paghi",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1454955765.687558,
            "question": "pagare (tu)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ordina, misto",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147696.177813,
            "question": "Maria orders mixed appetizers. Maria ___ l'antipasto ___.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "chiede, conto",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147615.5918999,
            "question": "Maria asks for the bill. Maria ___ il ____.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "chiedi",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147389.3245978,
            "question": "chidere (tu)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Lei prende il primo"
            ],
            "answer": "Lei (formal) prende il primo.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486061251.9745734,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You (formal) take the first course.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Shall I order the wine also",
                "Shall I order wine too?"
            ],
            "answer": "Shall I order wine, too?",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486406043.5499017,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ordino anche il vino?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "ordina",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1454955301.7132583,
            "question": "ordinare (lui/lei)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "La scuola e' vicino alla stazione.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1454955062.0453708,
            "question": "The school is next to the station.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "paga",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1454955344.6471367,
            "question": "Lei (pagare) con la carta di credito.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Yes, of course. A half a liter of the house red and a bottle of mineral water: still.",
                "Yes of course. A half a liter of the house red and a bottle of mineral water"
            ],
            "answer": "Yes, sure. Half a liter of the house red. And a bottle of mineral water, still.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486406076.4652414,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Si, certo: mezzo litro di (vino) rosso della casa. E una bottiglia di acqua minerale naturale.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "ho",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1454955783.3540568,
            "question": "avere (io)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Io ordino l'antipasto"
            ],
            "answer": "Io ordino l'antipasto.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486061178.31707,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I order the antipasto.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "chiede",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147393.792633,
            "question": "Lui (chiedere) il conto.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Paghiamo con la carta di credito.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1454696838.47554,
            "question": "We pay by credit card.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "I ask for",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1454955761.763497,
            "question": "Given the definition \"chiedo\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "i fiori di Paola sono in giardino"
            ],
            "answer": "I fiori di Paola sono in giardino.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147741.138092,
            "question": "Paola's flowers are in the garden.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "siamo, ristorante",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1454955604.7820046,
            "question": "We are are an Italian restaurant. ___ in un ___ italiano.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "tomato and basil",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147400.0810797,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"pmodoro e basilico\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Io prendo il contorno.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1454955102.9101303,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I take the side dish.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "vorrei le bruschette della casa"
            ],
            "answer": "Vorrei le bruschette della casa.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486148104.9891255,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I would like the bruschette of the house.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "le patate",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486061751.9402359,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the potatoes\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "delicious",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486406898.4798994,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"squisito/squisita/squisiti/squisite\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'acqua minerale",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486061747.3277237,
            "question": "Given the definition \"mineral water\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "paghiamo",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486406020.6508267,
            "question": "Noi (pagare) con la carta di credito.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "he/she asks for",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1454954722.8774521,
            "question": "Given the definition \"chiede\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Prendo i ravioli al ragu'.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1454955046.5482938,
            "question": "I'll have (take) the ravioli with meat sauce.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "L'automobile/la macchina di Luigi e' rossa",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1454954717.1031544,
            "question": "Luigi's car is red",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "And what are you having as a first course?",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1454696851.19554,
            "question": "Given the definition \"E cosa prendi per primo?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "mia mamma e' simpatica"
            ],
            "answer": "Mia mamma e' simpatica.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486148147.2442238,
            "question": "My mom is nice.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "you take the ravioli with meat sauce"
            ],
            "answer": "You (informal) take the ravioli with meat sauce.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486406895.2483015,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Tu prendi i ravioli al ragu'.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Io invece vorrei le penne al pomodoro e basilico: sono squisite"
            ],
            "answer": "Io invece vorrei le penne al pmodoro e basilico: sono squisite.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486061722.2936385,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I, on the other hand, would like the penne with tomato and basil sauce. It's delicious.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "I take the side dish.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1454696893.43254,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Io prendo il contorno.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "naturale/naturali",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1454696828.65654,
            "question": "Given the definition \"natural, non-carbonated, still\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Good idea! I'd like the pork roast with a side of potatoes instead.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1454955027.0656476,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Buona idea. Io invece vorrei il maiale al forno con contorno di patate.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "pago",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1454955787.6904929,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I pay\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "prendi",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1455122095.284631,
            "question": "prendere (tu)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Il bagno e' nuovo.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1455122101.964299,
            "question": "The bathroom is new.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "All right, I'll call the waiter right away.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1454954705.5547116,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Bene, chaimo subito il cameriere.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "prendo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147805.8360138,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I take\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "you take",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486061756.3486636,
            "question": "Given the definition \"prendi\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "chiedo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486406875.7963161,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I ask for\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "lui ordina il secondo"
            ],
            "answer": "Lui ordina il secondo.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486061219.0229843,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"He orders the main course.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "you order",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1454954682.001217,
            "question": "Given the definition \"ordini\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "I order",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1454955572.2812016,
            "question": "Given the definition \"ordino\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I'll take the ravioli; it's very good"
            ],
            "answer": "I'll have the ravioli; they're very good.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147279.5592103,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Prendo i ravioli; sono molto buoni.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "beefsteak"
            ],
            "answer": "the beefsteak",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486406015.5390582,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la bistecca\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sei",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486405918.048862,
            "question": "essere (tu)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "ordina",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1455116608.6965604,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"he/she orders\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I, on the other hand, would like the penne with tomatoes and basil sauce: it's exquisite"
            ],
            "answer": "I, on the other hand, would like the penne with tomato and basil sauce. It's delicious.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486061676.601143,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Io invece vorrei le penne al pmodoro e basilico: sono squisite.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "chiamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147369.9934568,
            "question": "Io (chiamare) il cameriere.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "She orders the fruit.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1454954677.3230543,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lei ordina la frutta.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "He takes the dessert.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1455116739.1885602,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lui prende il dolce.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "chiami",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147808.3316991,
            "question": "chiamare (tu)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "pago",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1454955717.2517428,
            "question": "pagare (io)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "dov'e' la farmacia"
            ],
            "answer": "Dove'e' la farmacia?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147875.8941174,
            "question": "Where is the pharmacy?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "paga",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1454955356.7714121,
            "question": "pagare (lui/lei)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ordino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486061167.056159,
            "question": "ordinare (io)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "tu ordini il primo"
            ],
            "answer": "Tu ordini il primo.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486061113.5611181,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You (informal) order the first course.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "la bistecca",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1454955252.3676417,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the beefsteak\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "You (formal) take the first course.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1454696814.55754,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lei (formal) prende il primo.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "ha",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1454955258.8198066,
            "question": "avere (lui/lei)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ordino, al",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486061693.744842,
            "question": "I order ravioli with meat sauce. Io ___ i ravioli ___ ragu'.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "siamo in cucina"
            ],
            "answer": "Siamo in cucina.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486061685.473506,
            "question": "We are in the kitchen",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the potatoes",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486407292.4075444,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"le patate\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ordini",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147648.2866626,
            "question": "Tu (ordinare) il pesce della casa.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "chiedi, caffe"
            ],
            "answer": "chiedi, caffe'",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486407286.503855,
            "question": "You ask for dessert and coffee. Tu ___ il dolce e il ___.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "chiedi",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486406324.8173673,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"you ask for\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ordini",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486061567.116031,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"you order\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "He orders the main course.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1454955141.4965332,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lui ordina il secondo.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "natural, non-carbonated, still",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1454954591.253199,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"naturale/naturali\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "prendiamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1455122050.1831214,
            "question": "Noi (prendere) il dolce ed il caffe'.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "prendo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1454954995.3960865,
            "question": "prendere (io)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "mineral water",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147316.4501731,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'acqua minerale\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "chiede",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486407274.595637,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"he/she asks for\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "I pay",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147284.159608,
            "question": "Given the definition \"pago\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "chiamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486407230.680852,
            "question": "chiamare (io)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ordini, griglia",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486407269.0517848,
            "question": "You order grilled fish and mixed salad. Tu ___ il pesce all ___ e l'insalata mista.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sono",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486061223.1111853,
            "question": "essere (io)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "he/she orders",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1454954626.2741532,
            "question": "Given the definition \"ordina\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "he/she pays",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1454955580.273617,
            "question": "Given the definition \"paga\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "he/she takes",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147604.861122,
            "question": "Given the definition \"prende\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "You (informal) order the first course.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1454955713.6076584,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Tu ordini il primo.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "pago, carta",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147441.4110892,
            "question": "I pay the check by credit card. Io ___ il conto con la ___ di credito.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "e'",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486405928.3488622,
            "question": "essere (lui/lei)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ordino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486406321.7683575,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I order\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "ordini",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1454954595.2852905,
            "question": "ordinare (tu)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "hai",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1454696504.75754,
            "question": "avere (tu)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "paghi",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1454955724.842416,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"you pay\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Yes, the meat is excellent. I'll have a beefsteak with a side of salad.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1454955244.9994912,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Si, la carne e' eccellente. Prendo una bistecca con contorno di insalata.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        }
    ]
}